REBECCA SATO: Hi.
And we're going to talk about self-image and writing.
And the reason this is worth talking about is because a writer and his or her self-image is very interrelated.
I know not everyone is going to agree with me and there have been very disturbed people, individuals who were excellent writers.
So I'm not saying that you can't be--there's a wide range of people in different mindsets that can write interesting things that are good and people want to read.
So that's not what I'm trying to say.
But if you want to be a happy writer, here's how to do it.
Okay.
So this is going to be about self-image.
And right now, I think this does apply to experienced writers as well but I'm primarily speaking to writers who are just starting out.
Okay.
Here's the "you" that others see.
Okay?
And the others, they might see you as a plumber, so let's just say that.
You're a plumber.
That's what you are to them.
Okay?
And here's the "you" that you see.
So this is you.
And you might see yourself as confused or--you know, you don't see yourself as a plumber.
Very few people see themselves as their job because you're not your job.
That's what you're doing right now but that doesn't capsulate your mind, heart, body and soul.
Maybe you feel like confused.
You're like, "I don't feel like I'm a plumber."
Not there's any wrong about being a plumber and if you're in love in being a plumber, that's awesome.
But let's say this is "you," okay?
And this right here is actually the real "you," and I realized that the word "real" is subjective.
But let's talk about this person, how to go from this to this and how to find this, and we're going to talk about that next.